[
  {
    "prompt": "1 + 4 * 19",
    "answer": 77,
    "time": 12000,
    "points": 2000
  },
  {
    "prompt": "16 + 13 * 12",
    "answer": 172,
    "time": 12000,
    "points": 2000
  },
  {
    "prompt": "17 + 3 * 15",
    "answer": 62,
    "time": 12000,
    "points": 2000
  },
  {
    "prompt": "5 + 13 + 11",
    "answer": 29,
    "time": 12000,
    "points": 2000
  },
  {
    "prompt": "14 * 3 * 6",
    "answer": 252,
    "time": 12000,
    "points": 2000
  },
  {
    "prompt": "17 + 3 * 17",
    "answer": 68,
    "time": 12000,
    "points": 2000
  },
  {
    "prompt": "9 * 19 * 14",
    "answer": 2394,
    "time": 12000,
    "points": 2000
  },
  {
    "prompt": "1 * 9 * 1",
    "answer": 9,
    "time": 12000,
    "points": 2000
  },
  {
    "prompt": "2 + 7 + 5",
    "answer": 14,
    "time": 12000,
    "points": 2000
  },
  {
    "prompt": "1 + 9 + 3",
    "answer": 13,
    "time": 12000,
    "points": 2000
  }
]